<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Working!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Working!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Jeff Mayeur</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 20:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Summing it up</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/summing-it-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 20:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/summing-it-up/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Sum it up, and be quick. The Basics Go HTML Template - This is the basic language that is used to inject dynamic content and logic into an otherwise static HTML Document Hugo Templates - Hugo uses the Go HTML Template to structure the a site, from the home page, to sub pages, to navigation, all of the facets of a Huge Site are driven through these templates Hugo Clarity&amp;rsquo;s Excerpt - This is the template I&amp;rsquo;m interested in, it renders the &amp;ldquo;Summary&amp;rdquo; that shows up on the root of this blog.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Is Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-is-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2024 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/where-is-hugo/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Why a TXT DNS Record is both necessary and fun when it comes to using a custom domain name for this blog
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It Starts Here</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-starts-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2024 20:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/it-starts-here/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Jeff What This site exists mostly for me collect things as they fly by. I&amp;rsquo;m not particularly expert at anything, but I&amp;rsquo;ve come to truly enjoy a wide array of &amp;ldquo;huh; what abouts&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; where I take the things I&amp;rsquo;ve seen before, hone them, and fit them into the future. Maybe this will only be useful for me. Maybe there&amp;rsquo;s something that can be borrowed and applied by others. In either case it gives me another tool to spelunk through my memory for tidbits I might want to repurpose.
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
